Guide to the University of Chicago University Extension Records 1892-1979
University of Chicago Library
- Series V: Institutes and Programs
  - Institute of Public Service, 1941-1942, G-L (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Institute of Public Service, 1941-1942, M-Z (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Institute of Public Service, 1941-1942, miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Engineering, Science and Management Defense Training Program, 1941-April 1942 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Engineering, May 1942-January 1943 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Engineering, February 1943-July 1944 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Great Books program, 1943-1944 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Great Books program, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Great Books program, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Great Books program, 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Great Books program, 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Great Books program, miscellaneous (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Midway USO, 1942-1945 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Foundations of American Democracy, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Executive Program, 1945-1958 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Basic Program of Liberal Education for Adults, 1949-1958 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Economic Education Program, Republic Steel, ca. 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Courses with special groups and organizations, 1953-1957 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Art Institute, 1953-1956 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Summer Program in Executive Development for Federal Administrators, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Woodlawn and urban matters, budget, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Woodlawn and urban matters, "The Metropolitan Area as a Racial Problem," 1957 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Woodlawn and urban matters, "People and Neighborhood Renewal," 1962 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Woodlawn and urban matters, "Renewing Chicago in the ‘60s," 1961 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Woodlawn and urban matters, reports and proposals, general, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Woodlawn and urban matters, reports and proposals, Woodlawn Services Council and Faculty-Community Committee, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Woodlawn and urban matters, reports and proposals, Woodlawn Services Council and Faculty-Community Committee, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Workshop in Local Government and Civic Affairs, 1958-1960 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Workshop in Local Government and Civic Affairs, instruction manual and evaluations (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Center for Programs in Government Administration, financial report, 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Series VI: Self-Study Project
  - General correspondence, 1933-1957 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - General correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Committee, D. Gale Johnson address, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Advisory Committee, letter to Chancellor Kimpton from D. G. Johnson, H. Kalven, R. Streeter, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Advisory Committee, report, 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Conspectus, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Conspectus, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Conspectus, "University College Today," June 1960 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Downtown Center Program, 1954-1961 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Fund for Adult Education grant, 1956-1958 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Project indexes, 1959-1962 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Project summaries (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Project 1A, "University College in the Post-World War II Period" (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Projects 2 and 5, "Purposes and Programmatic Criteria" (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Project 3, "Analysis of the Requirements of Subject Matter and Adult Education" (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Project 4, "Curriculum Analysis" (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Project 6, "Fine Arts Program" (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Project 6A, "A History of the Fine Arts Program" (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Project 7, "The Exercise of Power in American Society" (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Project 9B, "Extension into Suburbia" (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Project 10, "Can Liberal Education Be Self-Supporting?" (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Project 11, "Academic Program for Professional Students" (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Project 12, "Administration of the ACE Examination" (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Project 12A, "Academic Program" (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Project 12C, "Informal Program" (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Project 12G, "The Moment of Consciousness" (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Project 12H, "Analysis of Organizational Affiliations of University College Students" (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Project 12J, "Student ," pretest and suggestions for analysis (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Project 12J, "Student ," inventory and results (Box 22, Folder 4-9)
  - Project 12J, "Student ," "Evaluation and Improvement of Instruction" (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Project 13A, "Self-Study Materials Provided to the Boorstin Committee" (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Project 14, "Content Acquisition" (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Project 16, "Examination of Public Relations and Promotional Activities" (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Project 17, "Facilities of University College and Their Relation to Academic Purposes and Achievement" (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Project 17A, "Move to Campus?" (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Project 18, "Downtown Center Faculty" (Box 23, Folder 7-8)
  - Project 19, "Downtown Center Administrative Staff" (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Project 20, "Budgeting Standards, Purposes and Procedures" (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Project 21, "Costing and Pricing" (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Project 23, "Relationships Between the Quadrangles and University College" (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Project 25, "Counseling and Guidance" (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Project 26, "Basic Program" (Box 24, Folder 1-8)
  - Project 27, "Labor Union Programs" (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Project 27A, "Liberal Arts Curriculum for Trade Union Officers" (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Project 28, "Programs of Lay-Led Community Discussion Groups" (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Project 29, "Illinois Congress of Parents and Teachers-University College Parent Education Program" (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Project 33, "University College Faculty Governing Board" (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Project 37, "Human Relations Training Center" (Box 24, Folder 14-15)
  - Project 37, "Human Relations Training Center" (Box 25, Folder 1-4)
  - Project 38, "Current Programs and Services at Downtown Center" (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Project 39, "In the Area; Twenty Other Evening Colleges" (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Series VII: Union Research and Education Project/Union Leadership Program
  - General correspondence, 1951-1962 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - General correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Association, Frank London Brown, 1961-1963 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1960-1962 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - American Institute for Free Labor Development, proposals, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Carnegie Corporation, progress report, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "Collective Bargaining," syllabus and reading list, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Committee Governing the Internship Program for Union Officers, report, 1952-1953 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Communication Workers of America Union Education Directors, conference, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Consultants on the Union Leadership Program, report (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Discussion guide, "Collective Bargaining," 1958-1959 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Discussion guide, "Handling Minority Problems in the Shop and in the Union" (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Discussion guide, "Legislative Education" (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Discussion guide, "Looking Ahead to Retirement" (Box 26, Folder 9-10)
  - Discussion guide, "Public Education in a Free Society," 1959 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Discussion guide, "Senior Citizens in a Free Society" (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Discussion guide, "Union Leadership Program," 1959-1961 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Discussion guide, "Unions and Co-ops" (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Discussion guide, "Unions and the Changing American Society," 1957 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Advisory Board, 1957-1963 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Fund for Adult Education, 1958-1959 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Fund for the Republic, 1957-1963 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders, seminar, 1962-1963 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Illinois Sales and Use Taxes, seminar, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, proposals, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Labor Advisory Committee, general, 1961-1963 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Labor Advisory Committee, report, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Labor Workshop, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - "Man and Ideas in the Modern World; The Liberal Arts for Trade Unions," report, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - National Labor Relations Board policy changes, seminar, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - "Public Employment and Collective Bargaining," seminar, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Publicity and flyers (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - "Recession," conference, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Report, annual, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Report, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - "Railway Labor," seminar, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Research (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Second-year students (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Union Executive Program, proposal, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Union Executive Program, proposal, January 1958 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Union Executive Program, proposal, June 1958 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Union membership attitude survey, report, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Union membership attitude survey, report, "Liberal Education for Union Officials," 1958 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Union membership attitude survey, report, locals, 1952-January 1953 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Union membership attitude survey, report, locals, March 1953-June 1953 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Union membership attitude survey, report, locals, July 1953 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Union membership attitude survey, report, locals, undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - "Syllabus and Reading List on Collective Bargaining," January 1962 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Series VIII: Promotional and Informational Material
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, Lecture Association, and Public Lectures, 1899-1906 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1907-1908, 1908-1909 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1909-1910 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1910-1911 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1911-1912 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1912-1913 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1913-1914 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1914-1923 (bound) (Box 31)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1914-1915, 1915-1916 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1916-1917 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1917-1918 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1918-1919 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1919-1920 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1920-1921 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1921-1922 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, Lecture Association, and Public Lectures, 1922-1923 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1925-1926, 1926-1927 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1927-1928 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1928-1929 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1929/1930-1932/1933 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1933-1934, 1934-1935 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1935-1936 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1936-1937 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1937-1938, 1938-1939 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1939-1943 (bound) (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook, University College, 1908-1913 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1914-1916 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1917-1918 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1919-1921 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1922-1923 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1924 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1925 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1925-1929 (bound) (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1928-1930 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, 1930 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, University Open Lectures, January-August 1931 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, University College, September-December 1931 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, University College, January-August 1932 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, University College, September 1932-December 1933 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, University College, 1933-1935 (bound) (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, University College, 1935-1957 (bound) (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, University College, 1936-1938 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, University College, January-March 1939 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, University College, April-June 1939 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, University College, July-December 1939 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, University College, January-June 1940 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, University College, July-December 1940 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook, University College, 1941 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook, University College, 1942 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook, University College, January-August 1943 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook, University College, September-December 1943 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, University College, January-March 1944 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, University College, April-December 1944 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, University Orchestral Association, 1909-1910 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, University Orchestral Association, 1910-1911, 1911-1912 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, University Orchestral Association, 1912-1913, 1913-1914 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, University Orchestral Association, 1914-1915 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, University Orchestral Association, 1915-1916 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook, University Orchestral Association, 1916-1917 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook, University Orchestral Association, 1917-1918 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook, University Orchestral Association, 1918-1919 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook, University Orchestral Association, 1919-1920 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook, University Orchestral Association, 1920-1921 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook, University Orchestral Association, 1921-1922 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook, University Orchestral Association, 1922-1923 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook, University Orchestral Association, 1923-1924 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook, University Orchestral Association, 1924-1925 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook, University Orchestral Association, 1925-1931 (bound) (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, University Orchestral Association, 1931-1932 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, University Orchestral Association, 1932-1933 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, University Orchestral Association, 1933-1934 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, University Orchestral Association, 1934-1935, 1935-1936 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook, Institute of Public Service, 1941-1942 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1951 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Flyers and promotional materials, 1930s (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Flyers and promotional materials, 1940s (Box 42, Folder 7-8)
  - Flyers and promotional materials, 1950s (Box 43, Folder 1-4)
  - Flyers and promotional materials, 1960s (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Flyers and promotional materials, 1970s (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Flyers and promotional materials, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)